Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Writings, 1870-1962; 1909-1944; Series III; 16.94; 29 boxes
  - Writings of Stephen Vincent Benét
    - "For Those Who Are as Right as Any"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 56, Folder 1902)
    - "For Us"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1903)
    - "Foreword" to Gauley Mountain by Louise McNeill
      - Page proof, [1939] (Box 56, Folder 1904)
    - "Foreword" to [ The Metaphysical Sword ?] by Jeremy Ingalls
      - Typescript and typescript carbon, [1941] (Box 56, Folder 1905)
    - "Foreword" to Theory of Flight by Muriel Rukeyser
      - Galley proof, circa 1935 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3126)
    - "Freedom from Fear"
      - Draft, essay, typescript and typescript carbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1906)
      - Draft, essay, typescript, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1943 (Box 56, Folder 1907)
      - Draft, essay, typescript, corrected, with autograph manuscript notes in an unidentified hand, undated (Box 56, Folder 1908)
    - "Freedom from Want"
      - Draft, "Message," typescript carbon, 1943 March 7 (Box 56, Folder 1909)
    - "From the Earth to the Moon"
      - Outline, motion picture scenario, typescript carbon, 1935 September 23 (Box 56, Folder 1910)
    - "Funeral Instructions"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1911)
    - "The Gilded Weathercock"
      - Draft, story, typerscript carbon, signed, undated (Box 56, Folder 1912)
    - "Girl Child"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1913)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon (Box 56, Folder 1914)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected (2 copies), undated (Box 56, Folder 1915)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1916)
    - "The Girl Who Walked Home"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, signed, undated (Box 56, Folder 1917)
    - "Give Us This Day"
      - Radio script, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1942 December 28 (Box 56, Folder 1918)
    - "Glamour"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1919)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 56, Folder 1920)
    - "The Golden Corpse"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1921)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1922)
      - Printed version, poem, Twentieth Century Poetry, edited by John Drinkwater, annotated, 1929 (Box 56, Folder 1923)
    - "Good Picker"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1924)
    - "The Green Country"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1925)
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 56, Folder 1926)
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 56, Folder 1927)
    - "Hands"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1928)
    - "Hard Weather: (Rhode Island Coast)"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1929)
    - "Harpagus' Banquet"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 56, Folder 1930)
    - "Harrigan's Head"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1931)
    - "The Headless Horseman"
      - Draft, operetta, typescript and typescript carbon, signed, 1936 (Box 56, Folder 1932)
      - Draft, operetta, typescript carbon, with annotations by Mary Cole Hollingsworth, 1936–1938 (Box 56, Folder 1933)
    - "The Heart of Peggy O'Neal"
      - Draft (incomplete), play, typescript carbon, undated (Box 56, Folder 1934)
      - Draft, typescript carbon, corrected and annotated, 1924 (Box 57, Folder 1935)
    - "Heart's Blood"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected (2 copies), undated (Box 57, Folder 1936)
    - " The Heritage of America by Henry Steele Commager and Allan Nevins"
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, corrected, [1939?] (Box 57, Folder 1937)
    - "Hospital"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1938)
    - "Hunger"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, with proofreaders' marks, undated (Box 57, Folder 1939)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1940)
    - "Hymn of a Reader to the New York City Librarians"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1941)
    - "I Hate the Rich!"
      - Draft, song lyrics, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1942)
    - "If This Should Change"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1943)
      - Draft, poem autograph manuscript (photocopy) (2 copies), 1941 September 2 (Box 57, Folder 1944)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected and annotated, undated (Box 57, Folder 1945)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected and signed, undated (Box 57, Folder 1946)
    - "An Immoral Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, circa 1921 (Box 57, Folder 1947)
    - "In Regard to Henry Mayfield"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1948)
    - "Instructions for C. and F.C."
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1949)
    - "Into Egypt"
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1950)
      - Draft, typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1951)
      - Draft, typescript (incomplete), undated (Box 57, Folder 1952)
    - "Introduction" to unidentified work
      - Draft, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1953)
      - Draft, typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1954)
    - "Invocation"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1955)
    - "Iowa Corn"
      - Draft, [scenario for story?], typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1956)
    - "Irish Air: (New York City)"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1957)
    - "The Island"
      - Draft, novel (incomplete), typescript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1958)
    - "Jacob and the Indians"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1959)
    - James Shore's Daughter
      - Outline and draft pages, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1960)
      - Draft pages, autograph manuscript, corrected, typescript, and typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1961)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1962)
      - Draft, typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1963)
      - Page proofs, frontmatter, signed, 1934 (Box 57, Folder 1964-1965)
      - Book jacket, Doubleday edition, circa 1934 (Box 57, Folder 1966)
    - "Jaufre Rudel Beholds the Lady of Tripoli"
      - Copy, poem, typescript, undated (Box 57, Folder 1967)
    - Jean Clarambaux [by] Jean Tousseul
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, undated (Box 57, Folder 1968)
    - John Brown's Body
      - Draft fragments, autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1969)
      - Microfiche of autograph manuscript leaves, undated (Box 57, Folder 1970)
      - Draft, "Note," typescript, 1927 October (Box 57, Folder 1971)
      - Draft, "Prelude," typescript, corrected, undated (Box 57, Folder 1972)
      - Draft, Invocation through Book VII, autograph manuscript, typescript, and typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 58, Folder 1973-1974)
      - Draft, "Book Eight" (incomplete), autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 58, Folder 1975)
      - Draft, typescript carbon, with printer's annotations, bound, circa 1928 (Box 58, Folder 1976)
      - "Quotes," possibly for jacket copy, typescript carbon, undated (Box 58, Folder 1977)
      - Draft, jacket copy, typescript carbon, undated (Box 58, Folder 1978)
      - Book jacket, unidentified edition, undated (Box 58, Folder 1979)
      - Publicity, typescript mimeograph, undated (Box 58, Folder 1980)
    - Johnny Pye the Fool-killer
      - Draft, story, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 58, Folder 1981)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 58, Folder 1982)
      - Page proof, 1938 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3127)
      - Proof sheets (7 copies), 1938 (Box 58, Folder 1983)
    - "Jolly Roger"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 58, Folder 1984)
    - "Journey Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 58, Folder 1985)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, signed, undated (Box 58, Folder 1986)
    - "Jungle Man"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 58, Folder 1987)
    - "A Keepsake Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript [carbon?], undated (Box 58, Folder 1988)
    - "King David"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 58, Folder 1989)
    - "The King of Cats"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 1990)
      - "Suggestions Stephen Vincent Benet Has Made About Developing 'The King of Cats'," typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 1991)
    - "Ku Klux"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 1992)
    - "A Lady Orders a Fan"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 1993)
    - "The Land Where There Is No Death"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 1994)
    - "The Last of the Legions"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 1995)
    - "Last Song of the Trojan Light Infanty"
      - Copy, poem, typescript, annotated, undated (Box 59, Folder 1996)
    - Lee's Lieutenants: A Study in Command by Douglas Southall Freeman
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, circa 1942 (Box 59, Folder 1997)
    - The Lees of Virginia by Burton J. Hendrick
      - Draft, review, typescript carbon, corrected, circa 1935 (Box 59, Folder 1998)
    - "Legend"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 1999)
    - "A Letter to Hitler"
      - Radio script, typescript mimeograph, annotated, 1942 September 29 (Box 59, Folder 2000)
    - "A Life at Angelo's"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 2001)
    - "Listen to the People"
      - Draft, radio script, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2002)
      - Draft, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2003)
      - Typescript mimeograph, corrected (3 copies), 1941 (Box 59, Folder 2004)
      - "Revised pages," typescript mimeograph, corrected (2 copies), 1941 (Box 59, Folder 2005)
      - Typescript mimeograph, 1943 July 5 (Box 59, Folder 2006)
    - "Litany for Dictatorships"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon (3 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2007)
    - "Little Brownstone House"
      - Draft, song lyrics, typescript (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2008)
    - "Little Testament"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2009)
    - "Lost In a Snow Storm"
      - Draft, juvenilia, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2010)
    - "The Lost Wife"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2011)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2012)
    - "The Loves of the Roses"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 2013)
    - "The Lucky Fist"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2014)
    - "Memorandum by Stephen Vincent Benet"
      - Draft, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 2015)
    - "Memory"
      - Draft, poem, typescript and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2016)
    - "A Memory Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2017)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2018)
    - "Merry Christmas"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, corrected, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 2019)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, 1927 (Box 59, Folder 2020)
    - "Metropolitan Nightmare"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2021)
    - "The Minister's Books"
      - Draft, story, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2022)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2023)
    - "Minor Litany"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2024)
    - "The Miracle"
      - Draft, "story idea," typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2025)
      - Draft, "story idea," typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 2026)
    - "Miracle Play"
      - Draft, radio script, autograph manuscript, typescript mimeograph, and typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2027)
    - "Moon-Island"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, signed, undated (Box 59, Folder 2028)
    - "Most Unforgettable Character"
      - Draft, biographical sketch, typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2029)
      - Draft, biographical sketch, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 59, Folder 2030)
    - "Mr. President, Ladies and Gentlemen"
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 59, Folder 2031)
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 2032)
    - "Muriel Rukeyser"
      - Draft, [introduction?], typescript carbon, undated (Box 59, Folder 2033)
    - "Name Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2034)
    - "Nightmare at Noon"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 59, Folder 2035)
    - "Nightmare for Future Reference"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2036)
    - "Nightmare Number Three"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2037)
    - "Nightmare With Angels"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2038)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2039)
    - "Nomenclature"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, signed, undated (Box 60, Folder 2040)
    - "A Nonsense Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2041)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2042)
    - "Notes To Be Left in a Cornerstone"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected (4 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2043)
    - "November Prothalamion"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2044)
    - "Ode to the Austrian Socialists"
      - Draft, poem, typecript carbon, corrected (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2045)
    - "Ode to Walt Whitman"
      - Draft fragment, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2046)
      - Draft, typescript, with printer's annotations, 1935 April (Box 60, Folder 2047)
    - "O'Halloran's Luck"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2048)
    - "Oil of Gladness"
      - Draft, story, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2049)
    - "Old Man Hoppergrass"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2050)
    - "An Old Woman [?]"
      - Draft, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2051)
    - "On D[?] Webs In a Work Room"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2052)
    - "On Hearing a Song Sparrow"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2053)
    - "One of the Gods"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2054)
      - Draft, story, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2055)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (3 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2056)
    - "Operation--City Hospital"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2057)
    - "Outline"
      - Draft, story idea, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2058)
    - "Philadelphia"
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2059)
      - Draft, address, typescript and typescript carbon (3 copies), corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2060)
    - "Pledge"
      - Drafts, autograph manuscript, typescript, and typescript carbon, corrected, circa 1941 (Box 60, Folder 2061)
    - "Poem Delivered on Alumni Day, May 6, 1933…"
      - Draft, typescript mimeograph, [1933?] (Box 60, Folder 2062)
    - "Poems and Battle Songs"
      - Drafts, typescript, autograph manuscript, typescript, and typescript carbon, corrected, 1912-1919, undated (Box 60, Folder 2063)
    - "Poetry"
      - Draft, address, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2064)
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2065)
    - "Possible Points of Agreement"
      - Draft, typescript and typescript carbon, 1940 May 26 (Box 60, Folder 2066)
    - "Praise God and Pass the Ammunition"
      - Draft, "synopsis of a proposed radio program," typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2067)
    - "A Prayer for the United Nations"
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2068)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2069)
    - "Preface"
      - Galley proof, corrected, of preface to The Orphan Angel by Elinor Wylie, 1932 (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3128)
    - "Princess Pauper"
      - Draft, synopsis, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2070)
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2071)
    - "The Proud Man"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected and signed, undated (Box 60, Folder 2072)
    - R. E. Lee [by] Douglas Southall Freeman
      - Draft, review, typescript, circa 1935 (Box 60, Folder 2073)
    - "Radio"
      - Draft, [address?], typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2074)
      - Draft, [address?], typescript and typescript carbon (3 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2075)
    - "Radio"
      - Draft, [interview?], typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2076)
    - "The Raveled Sleeve"
      - Galley proof, story, undated (Box 124 (Oversize), Folder 3129)
    - "Recrimination"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2077)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2078)
    - "Red Lights, Green Lights"
      - Draft, song lyrics, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2079)
    - "Remarks Addressed To Mother Nature…"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2080)
    - "Remarks from a Back Row Seat By an Amateur Propagandist"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, with autograph manuscript notes on verso, undated (Box 60, Folder 2081)
    - "Renewal"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 60, Folder 2082)
    - "Reply"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 60, Folder 2083)
    - "Rosemary's Song in Winter"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2084)
    - "R[o]und Table"
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 60, Folder 2085)
    - "A Sad Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 60, Folder 2086)
    - "The Salem Skipper: (Colonial America)"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2087)
    - "Sarah Spry"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2088)
    - "The Scapegoats"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2089)
    - "The School of Fortune"
      - Draft, story, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2090)
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2091)
    - "Schooner's Class"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2092)
    - Selected Works of Stephen Vincent Benet
      - Draft, dedication page, autograph manuscript, circa 1942 (Box 61, Folder 2093)
      - Page proofs (incomplete), 1942 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3130)
      - Page proofs of dedication and introduction, "printer's set," corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1942 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3131)
    - Semi-Centennial by Leonard Bacon
      - Draft, review, typescript and typescript carbon, circa 1939 (Box 61, Folder 2094)
    - "Sheff Monthly"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, annotated, undated (Box 61, Folder 2095)
    - "Short Ode"
      - Draft, poem, typescript and typescript carbon (3 copies), undated (Box 61, Folder 2096)
    - "Silver Jemmy"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon, annotated, undated (Box 61, Folder 2097)
    - "Skindeep"
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, and typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2098)
    - "A Snake Never Dies Until Sundown: A Play in One Act"
      - Draft, play, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2099)
    - "Snowfall"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2100)
    - "Some Contemporary Aspects of Literature"
      - Draft, address, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2101)
    - "Song"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2102)
      - Draft, poem, typescript, undated (Box 61, Folder 2103)
    - "Song About Children"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2104)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2105)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2106)
    - "Song for Three Soldiers"
      - Draft, typescript, with autograph manuscript notes on verso, and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 61, Folder 2107)
    - "Song of the Ph[eo]nix"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, undated (Box 61, Folder 2108)
    - "The Songs of Dear Old Yale"
      - Draft, poems, typescript and typescript carbon, 1917 (Box 61, Folder 2109-2110)
    - "The Soul's Colloquy with the Person"
      - Draft, poem, autograph manuscript, 1930 May (Box 61, Folder 2111)
    - Spanish Bayonet
      - Draft, "[Part] 4, The Fire on the Beach," autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2112)
      - Draft, "Part 4, The Fire on the Beach," typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2113)
    - "Sparrow"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2114)
    - "Speech for Heinz Hour"
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2115)
    - "Speech for Massey"
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2116)
    - "Spring, Gentle Spring"
      - Draft, song lyric, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2117)
    - "A Story by Angela Poe"
      - Draft, story, typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 61, Folder 2118)
    - "The Street of Martyrs"
      - Draft, [story?], autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2119)
    - "Stubborn Fig"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, corrected, undated (Box 61, Folder 2120)
    - "Susie: (A Bar-Room Ballad)"
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, undated (Box 61, Folder 2121)
    - Tales Before Midnight
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1939 (Box 61, Folder 2122)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, with proofreaders' marks and printer's annotations, 1939 (Box 62, Folder 2123)
      - Galley proof, corrected, 1939 August 31 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3132)
      - Page proof, corrected, 1939 September 21 (Box 125 (Oversize), Folder 3133)
    - "Tell Me Why"
      - Draft, story, typescript, corrected and signed, undated (Box 62, Folder 2124)
      - Draft, story, typescript and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 62, Folder 2125)
    - "Telling a Story in Prose"
      - Draft, address, typescript carbon, undated (Box 62, Folder 2126)
    - "Tercentenary Ode"
      - Copy, poem, typescript, circa 1938 (Box 62, Folder 2127)
    - "Thanks"
      - Draft, poem, typescript, with autograph manuscript notes on verso, undated (Box 62, Folder 2128)
      - Draft, poem, typescript carbon, corrected (2 copies), undated (Box 62, Folder 2129)
    - "Thanksgiving"
      - Draft, essay, typescript and typescript carbon (2 copies), undated (Box 62, Folder 2130)
      - Draft, essay, typescript carbon (3 copies), undated (Box 62, Folder 2131)
    - "Thanksgiving Day"